It happened during the first landing on Izune!
Did our kinsman agree to help the Orcs?
Koll agreed to release Skulnar's spirit? Unbelievable!
So that's how it all happened! Brus's blood helped find Isa...
And yet he abandoned this oath. To save Isa!
None of us could have imagined such a thing! Our lost brother!
That's why no one could find Isa! The Thread Keepers hid it well.
A sad story. It's a pity that this happened. But there was no other choice...
It turns out that Koll Sharp... is your ancestor, Gerda.
That's why there was always one Gibberling in our family.
A bond severed two centuries ago!
Can we bring Isa back to the world?
But at what cost? Skulnar will be free again!